do I
на его ли
press the day,
давлю день
look, I ask people from Russia
смотрите я у людей из россии спрашивать
how you feel about the war in Ukraine
как вы относитесь к войне в украине
and what it is forced by
а чем она вынуждена
8-year-olds and were able to agree on white
8-летним и смогли договориться по белому
had to defend so well and
пришлось защищать так хорошо а что там
what happened with the Nazis that they had to
такое было с нацистами что пришлось
attack Ukraine and you know  I want to
нападать на украину а вы знаете я хочу
figure it out, you know that for 8 years
разобраться вы знаете что 8 лет
you are from what you are from the Donbass myself I am from the Urals from the Urals
вы вы из какой вы из донбасса сами я с
fangi days from the Urals that
урала с урала фанги дней с урала что
in the 15th year what they did there
в 15-м году что что там делали
how they
как
fought
воевали
took up arms, that is, I didn’t understand Yes, that is,
ополчился то есть я не понял да то есть
you Russian mercenary arrived  from the Urals
вы русский наемник приехали из урала и
and fought,
воевали а
why did you fight for
почему вот вы воевали вот что вас за
your ideals,
свои идеалы
tell me interestingly from the Urals
расскажите интересно с урала
support for the Russian language,
поддержка русского языка во первых
firstly, firstly, secondly,
во первых во вторых защиты
you know,
знаете
I understand the support of the Russian language, that
я так понял поддержка русского языка то
is, you honor the Russian language, Russian
есть вы чтите русский язык русскую
literature, I understand correctly, yes, but
литературу я правильно понимаю да а вот
for example, you can tell me some
например можете назвать мне какую-то
poem by Alexander Sergeyevich Pushkin,
поэму александра сергеевича пушкина
I can read it to you,
могу вам прочитать
tell me what are Pushkin’s poems, Eugene
расскажите какие есть поэмы пушкина
Onegin Ruslan and Lyudmila, if
онегин
you want, you almost don’t need it  I
хотите вам почти не не надо там не
don’t understand at school they taught there, for example,
понимаю в школе там учили например вот
tell me what else, because I’m
скажите какие еще потому что мне
interested in telling me the girl one of the
интересно говорят мне девушка одна
previous stories of Pushkin is great and the world
предыдущих весту пушкин велики и мировой
writer, I think he wrote a lot of things
писатель я думаю он очень много чего то
since you are such an admirer of Russian
написал раз вы такие почитатель русской
I know, yes, it turns out you are only two
знаю знаю да то получается вы только два
works of Pushkin before  You can also
произведения пушкина до можете назвать
name Anna Karenina, so remember,
еще анну каренину так вспомним
you will see Solemacher wanted to catch you,
увидите солемахер хотел вас подловить
yes, a
его да
cunning
хитра
educated person, well, so
образованный человек хорошо так вот
look, you lived in the Urals that in the
смотрите вы жили на урале that
fifteenth year,
пятнадцатом году
Ukrainian, enter I am a poorly educated
украинский вписать я плохо образованный
exchange person, you said there I came for the Russian language
обмену вы сказали там я за русский язык
,
приехал
don’t look, I’ll just explain here you
не смотрите я просто объясню вот вы
they said that you came to defend the Russian
сказали что вы приехали защищать русский
languages, I wanted to see, or
языки я захотел посмотреть или
does the Russian language really
действительно русский язык для вас
mean something to you, so ask yes, and
что-то значит так поэтому и спроси да а
now look, you lived in the Urals, then
теперь смотрите вот вы жили на урале то
there is a thousand kilometers from about 200, you
там тысячу километров от где-то 200
know, yes, that's who you worked before
извите да вот вы кем работали до того
how did you go to fight in ukraine,
как поехали воевать в украину
but not that is, it turns out that you
только не то есть получается вот вы
worked as a
работали токарем токарем так и
turner  15 they worked there and
не 15 там работали так и
took it and went to fight in the coals, well,
взяли и поехали воевать в угли ну так
to
вот
fight to fight in Ukraine is to fight to
воевать воевать украины это воевать
fight for people before who
воевать за людей до которые террористами
were terrorists,
были на
so if you defend
вот если вы защищаете свой
yours, wait,
подожди
come on and let's do it so who was
давай и давайте так давайте так кто был
whoever I want I want to sort it out easier
ни я хочу я хочу разобраться легче
sort out
разобраться
after such a character with a batch zico from the
после такого персонажа батчатом зико из
forgotten Urals when the car to win 3 in the
забытую урала when the car to win 3-х в
fifteenth lesson, so for the Russian language of
пятнадцатом уроке так за русский язык
Russian people
русских людей
returned to 6 - sub-regions to moisture and a
вернулся до 6 - подобласти к влаге и
prosperous Donetsk people's
процветающей донецкой народной
republic
республике
there is such a thing I can stand people on, we have found a
есть таким выношу люди на у нас найдено
sara lack of such and  such types of
сара недостатку такое и уж такие виды
ice, these were opinions not for money,
льда вот эти были мнения не за деньги
like yes, I helped there for the idea
типа да я там помогал за идею
blah blah blah for money
бла-бла-бла за бабки
immediately nice and the money stopped and the idea
сразу мило и бабки перестал и идея
was gone thanks to sit down to the sieves that's
пропала благодаря сиди бы до ситов вот
what kind of people lobach here calling Pushkin h2c
какие люда лобач сюда назвав пушкина h2c
hake for 2 creatures  Nabil tires jumped out of
хека на 2 твари набиль шины выскочила
strength
силы
to defend and the Russian Alaeva effective
защищать и российскому алаева эффективен
lining from Anna Karenina alone in heat
подклад из анны карениной alone in heat
camelina knowing Dasha the cycle of schools at school shaya
рыжик зная даша цикл школ в школе шайа в
what is the whole system so places but p  for 8
чем вся так местам система но побачылы 8
months the shah tariff sounded 6 rivers
месяцев шах тариф звучали 6 реки там
fought there so for
воевала так за
not golden someone and why are we
не золотисто кто-то и чего есть мы
Bachimo that
бачимо что
coupe such a shah tariff with souls tariff so
coupe таких шах тариф со душах тариф так
why so and motorola cysts so on
чего так и кистах моторолы так далее
mukla eats us once that it’s just there
муклы нам раз поедает что это просто там
places on us she  climbed up and
места на нас она забралась и
battles of the evil euls to name Isa and the
битвы еулов злых назвать ису и
territory of the workshop propaganda low chose the
территории цеха пропаганда низкий chose
execution of the mind you still wouldn’t have them again I didn’t
выполнение разуме ты еще их бы раз я не
go to the donbass to the donbass 2014 roadside
зашла в донбасс на донбасс 2014 roadside
are easy with their
are easy своим
staff and people of you like this and the type of
кадровым и людьми из вас таким и типу
volunteer did not recruit any and through the
добровольцем никаких набирал и через
special life of the structure so forgot  about
специальные жизни структуры так забыл об
spooky in the donbass that
spooky на донбассе то
word is so hit glory to ukraine
слово так поразить слава украине